Then you can see here that we have the
model, which is Genjutsu, and the
quality, you can pick 480p, 720, and
1080p. For this particular example, I
used 720p, and that's a 13-second clip.
So, therefore, it consumes 91 credits.
After you send it in, it takes about 4
to 5 minutes, and these are the results.
>> I will spit your head out.
>> But you have learned nothing.
Poseidon's sons are not stupid, huh?
They're not foolish. You eat me, then
you kill all the secrets of the world.
>> What secrets, huh?
>> What secrets?
>> Anticlus, the wine.
>> All right. So, what if we wanted to take
that one scene, clip it, and change the
characters a bit, or enhance the
characters? This is where we're going to
go to ChatGPT now and generate the
characters that we want to see to
replace those. So, I went ahead and open
up a ChatGPT window. I took a screenshot
of the Cyclops,
and then I gave it a reference image
just for color purposes, because I
wanted the revised version of the
Cyclops to be a bit colder,
so it looks more like a modern film. So,
you can see here that I generated the
character sheet with the prompt that I
used right over here. You can screenshot
it, take a look at it. But this is a
sec- the reference image just for the
color of it. Once I generated the
character sheet, I saved it, and I moved
ahead to my second character, which was
this guy right over here.
I wanted to change him a little bit to
look more like a Viking with red hair.
So, that's what I prompted. And this is
the character that we have.
And you can change the character
completely, you can enhance them, you
can do whatever you want. But this is a
really cool use of AI if you want to
take the camera movement from a scene,
even restore old footage like I did here
with your own new character. So, now
that we have our footage saved,
We downloaded the Odyssey mini-series
from 1997
from Internet Archive. And if you don't
know the site, this is the home page.
And here it just tells you a little bit
about it. You can download millions of
videos, movies, music, websites that are
archived in here for
public domain purposes, Creative
Commons, uh education. But in this case,
this series is copyrighted, so we're
going to use it on the fair use, and you
can download the entire hour and
27-minutes part one,
take it to your video editor of choice,
and just clip a portion that you want to
restore. You can see here you can scrub
through the whole thing and look for
something that you're interested in. Now
that I have the footage and I have my
two reference images, I want to go ahead
and take a look at Hicksfield Genjutsu,
which is Hicksfield's newest
application. This is where I was able to
build a whole prompt, attach the
reference video when I clipped it, and
use the reference images. Let's scrub
through here again and watch this so you
can see.
>> I will spit your head out.
>> But you will learn nothing.
Poseidon's sons are not stupid, huh?
>> You can see how great the quality is. If
you I don't know if you can see it cuz
it's pretty small, but I'm going to
download this and put it bigger on the
screen so you guys can see it.
>> They're not foolish. You eat me, then
you kill all the secrets of the world.
>> What secrets, huh?
>> The best way that I found to use this is
by actually typing in the prompt.
Because you can use it in two ways. So
if I were to go in here and get my Let
me reload this so you can guys can see
what I did here. If I do rerun,
Oh, I'm out of credits. So that's not
going to help. Let me see if I do copy
it. There you go. That's what I wanted
to do, copy it. I downloaded the video,
clipped it, and here's the original
video right over here.
>> your head out.
>> But you will learn nothing.
And then, I put the two reference images
from ChatGPT in here. And this is what I
was getting to.
You can leave the prompt off and just
send it this way, but I found the best
results if you actually put a prompt in
there. And don't worry, you don't have
to actually type in the prompt yourself.
Let me paste it here so you can see.
It's a long, long prompt. You don't have
to type all of it because I already
created this skill that you can have.
I'm going to leave the link to the skill
in the description. And then all you
have to do, this is a Claude session, or
you can go to maybe use the skill in
ChatGPT if you would like, but you'd
have to get the skill file and give it
to ChatGPT and say, "Hey, read this file
and adapt it to your own
uh methods because this is specially for
Claude, okay? The skill, what it does is
you give it the reference images, the
two reference images here, and say, "I
have two reference images that I want to
use to replace the following
characters." And then you show the
characters from the video. So, I'm not
downloading and uploading the video into
Claude. I'm simply giving Claude the
screenshot of those characters from my
video. Claude cannot see videos or read
videos at this moment. So, right now,
that's what you want to do. You want to
create the images and then give the
references right here from the clip. And
this is simply what the what I wrote.
Here are some characters from the
original Odyssey film, which is really
mini-series, TV series. I have an entire
scene that I want to rebuild with the
new characters. I will upload video one,
and then I want to upload these two
characters. Please give me a prompt for
this. When I said upload video one, I
don't mean it to Claude. I mean it here
to Hicksfield. So, the skill will take
this short prompt right here,
and it's going to give me the entire
prompt for Hicksfield. See, edit video
one, replace the long-haired smiling
warrior with image two. So, So, gives
you the entire prompt that you can
simply copy. Once you get to Higgsfield
in here, you want to first upload your
video and then your images because once
you
copy your prompt, it's going to auto tag
those references. Those assets are going
to be auto tagged in here. If you were
to paste the prompt before you uploaded
the assets, it would not work. It
wouldn't know what to tag. So, that's
why it's important to upload your assets
first and be sure that they are uploaded
and not still loading before you paste
this entire prompt. And then here, you
just want to double-check to make sure
that look, video one is really the video
that we're seeing here cuz you can have
multiple videos. And then that image two
is indeed the man and that image one is
the Cyclops. So, you can see here that
it look, you can match the intention.
One-eyed giant with image one. Then you
can see here that we have the model,
which is Genjutsu, and the quality, you
can pick 480p, 720, and 1080p. For this
particular example, I use 720p and
that's a 13-second clip. So, therefore
it consumes 91 credits. After you send
it in, it takes about 4 to 5 minutes. If
you want to try out Higgsfield Genjutsu
for yourself, it can kind of be hard to
find it on the website. So, I'm going to
leave a link down in the description so
you can go directly to this page and
start generating. You can also see the
other samples of what you can create
with it. Thank you for watching, guys,
and I'll see you next time.
>> I will spit your head out.
>> But you will learn nothing.
Poseidon's sons are not stupid, huh?
They're not foolish. You eat me, then
you kill all the secrets of the world.
>> What secrets, huh?
>> [music]